corporateperks.com 2016-11-07

# Privacy Policy - Corporate Perks

We are committed to protecting your privacy. At no time will we trade, sell, or distribute organization specific or personal information, including email addresses or other user IDs, to any individual, company, vendor or organization, in ways other than disclosed in this privacy statement. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Customer Service via the ['Contact Us'](https://www.corporateperks.com/feedback/index/uSource/PRIV) tool, leaving your comments, questions or concerns. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact the Better Business Bureau [http://www.BBB.org](http://www.bbb.org/). The Better Business Bureau will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

Next Jump, Inc. complies with the EU Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Next Jump's certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor>. 

Your first name, last name, valid email address, and zip code represent the only pieces of personal information you must submit to access Corporate Perks. In certain instances, other demographic data or payment card information will be collected, but not required. Corporate Perks uses this information to provide the benefits/services associated with the program. 

Additionally, Corporate Perks collects click-stream data and other preference information on its users in order to improve the design and vendor selection of the site. Click-stream data represents a page-by-page history of a person's site usage. 

Corporate Perks is a portal through which users access discounts redeemable at selected vendors. In most cases, online purchases facilitated by the Corporate Perks portal are subject to the privacy policies of the Web Site where that transaction is conducted. In a few cases; however, Corporate Perks itself functions as the vendor and must collect additional personal information, described later in this privacy policy, to complete the online transaction. 

When users register a payment card through Corporate Perks's registered card program, we collect payment card information for the purpose of tracking transactions from participating registered card program vendors. Collected card information is used in the authentication of the payment card with our financial services partners (card issuers, processors, and network associations such as American Express, Master Card, and VISA). Corporate Perks will also collect, process and store transaction data from vendors participating in the registered card program for the purpose of applying the appropriate discount to the users payment card and to improve the design and vendor selection of the site. 

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a spouse/family member about our site, we will ask you for your spouse/family member's name and email address. We will automatically send your spouse/family member a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Next Jump, Inc. stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your spouse/family member may contact Next Jump, Inc. [Customer Service](https://www.corporateperks.com/feedback/index/uSource/PRIV) to request that we remove this information from our database. 

Next Jump Inc. requires your first name, last name, and email address for the following reasons: 

1\. To provide a point of contact for communicating correspondence, including your personal password, technical issues that may arise and periodic reminders that you may request (on an opt-in basis) as a Corporate Perks user.

2\. To assign a name to your user id and password.

3\. To verify your affiliation with the organization using Next Jump, Inc. Corporate Perks. 

4\. To provide the benefits/services associated with Corporate Perks. 

Click-stream data can help determine the popularity of vendors, offers and site features with our audience, allowing us to develop a better site. An individual user's click-stream data is kept in the strictest confidence, and will never be distributed to any party outside of Next Jump, Inc. 

Next Jump, Inc. only shares aggregated data to third party vendors, but it will not disclose information specific to any user or organization, including email address except as described in this privacy policy. This information represents a generic overview of our users' collective viewing habits and allows vendors to modify their discounts based on user traffic. To fulfill certain purchases by you, it may be necessary for us to share your information with our partners. Additionally, some participating organizations have requested monthly reports of traffic on Corporate Perks. These reports will reveal only the aggregated viewing habits of Corporate Perks visitors from that organization. The reports will not disclose the user name, login ID or any other personal information of users, including email address.   
When users give money to nonprofits through our Charitable Giving program, we will share personal information including email address, with the chosen nonprofit only if permitted. Nonprofits use the contact information for acknowledgment purposes and to provide tax receipts. We will not share this information unless you **opt-in** and thereby indicate to us to notify the nonprofit of your gift. If you wish to discontinue receiving information from the respective nonprofit, please contact them directly. 

When users RSVP to an in-store retail event, limited information is provided to the participating merchant in the form of the guest list for admittance into the private event. This information is limited to your first name and last name, and if you will be bringing a guest. 

When users register a payment card through the registered card program, transaction data will be shared with their payment card issuer and processor solely for the purpose of applying the appropriate discount to the users payment card. 

Next Jump employs third parties to perform specific functions on our behalf. Examples include, without limitation, hosting services, vaulting and customer service. Some providers have access to personal data to provide a service to us, but may not use it for anything other than intended purposes. 

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. Next Jump, Inc. uses cookies on the site(s). Next Jump, Inc. does link the information stored in cookies personally identifiable information, including email address, you submit while on the site(s). 

Next Jump, Inc. uses both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are used to make it easier for you to navigate the site(s). A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. 

Persistent cookies are set to store an encrypted link to your account information, so you don't have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable Next Jump, Inc. to track and target the interests of users to enhance the experience on the site(s). If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. 

Some business partners (e.g., advertisers, tracking utilities) use cookies and Web beacons on their site(s). Next Jump, Inc. has no access to or control over these tracking technologies. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by our sites and private label subdomains delivered by Next Jump, Inc. only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

Next Jump, Inc. will not send unsolicited emails to registered users of Corporate Perks without consent. Additionally, users may choose to receive Corporate Perks correspondence, including email reminders of specific vendor offers and Corporate Perks newsletters. The "my account" channel on the site displays the correspondence you've elected to receive, and provides the option to unsubscribe from future Corporate Perks related emails. 

All emails sent by Corporate Perks contain directions on how to unsubscribe from future correspondence. At any time, users may opt out of Corporate Perks related correspondence by visiting the [Contact Us](https://www.corporateperks.com/feedback/index/uSource/PRIV) page. Users may also access their personal information, including email address to make edits in the "My Account" section of the website. 

In addition, a registered user who wishes that their personal information, including email address to be completely removed from the Corporate Perks database should use the [Contact Us](https://www.corporateperks.com/feedback/index/uSource/PRIV) page. We will respond to your request within twenty [20] business days. An individual's complete removal of his or her personal information from the database negates that individual's ability to login to Corporate Perks. 

Users will be notified of changes or revisions to this privacy policy, including our email practices, by a notice posted on the Corporate Perks login page. The notice will contain a link, whereby the Privacy policy can be examined in full. In this way registered users are made aware of policy changes prior to shopping or browsing the Web Site. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. As always, a user who is not amenable to the conditions of a revised privacy policy may opt out of Perks by means outlined earlier in this document. 

Next Jump, Inc. uses an outside shipping company to fulfill orders, and a payment card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain share, store or use personally identifiable information, including email address, for any other purposes. 

Next Jump, Inc. uses other third parties to process payment card transactions on the site(s). When you sign up for programs directly related to Corporate Perks, Next Jump, Inc. will share first name, last name, payment card information and billing address as necessary for the third party to provide that service. No other information is shared with third parties for this purpose. For Registered Card transactions, the transaction and discount information is shared with the users payment card issuer and processor only for the purpose of applying the appropriate discount to the user's payment card 

These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information, including email address, for any other purpose. 

Corporate Perks is a portal that provides access to exclusive discounts redeemable at the point of purchase at a certain vendor's online or offline location. In rare cases, Corporate Perks may serve as both vendor and portal, and will collect certain information necessary to complete an online purchase. Like every online purchase, you will be required to submit the following information to buy an item where Corporate Perks is the vendor: 

• Shipping or billing address or both  
• Credit card information  
• Day time phone number  
• Email address 

In all cases, any transaction conducted through Corporate Perks is secured and encrypted with SSL technology, and certified by Verisign. Hence, you may submit any sensitive data to this site with the assurance that it will remain protected. 

Again, Corporate Perks will never compromise your personal privacy. Information, including email addresses, submitted to carry out a transaction where Next Jump, Inc. is the vendor is kept in the highest confidentiality, and is absolutely never shared with outside parties in ways other than disclosed in this privacy statement. 

Corporate Perks is a portal that enables users to purchase discounted products on the Web Sites of participating vendors. Each vendor maintains its' own privacy policy that you should be familiar with before you submit your personal information. Our privacy policy is not applicable on any of the vendor sites. Therefore, it is important for a potential buyer to familiarize himself with the privacy policies of each vendor. 

Next Jump, Inc will never transmit personal identifiers, including name, email address, or user ids to any participating vendor. Clicking on a vendor site through Corporate Perks does not result in the transmission of your personal information to that vendor 

Although your privacy is of paramount concern to us, Next Jump, Inc. cannot reasonably be expected to suppress information where the withholding of such information represents a violation of federal or state law. 

Next Jump, Inc. reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information, including email address, as required by law and when it is believed that disclosure is necessary to protect Next Jump, Inc.'s rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on the site(s). 

As a user of Corporate Perks, you consent to our collection and storage of your personal information, including email address, (as defined above) in our database, and to our use of aggregated and non-personal information generated by the viewing habits of our users. 

Corporate Perks uses tracking to apply WOWPoints for transactions and to optimize the overall user experience on the site. At this time, as with many services, Next Jump Inc., does not alter behavior or change the service based on a browser's Do Not Track requests. 

Next Jump Inc does not disclose any personally identifiable information to third parties that would allow a third party to track a users online activities over time and across web sites. The exception is when items are purchased directly through Corporate Perks. In these cases, information may be shared with the merchant to fulfill the transaction. In addition, Next Jump Inc. does not allow third parties to collect personally identifiable information about a user that would allow the third party to track online activities over time or across different websites. 

Next Jump, Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy. Next Jump, Inc. does not sell, trade, give away, or rent personal or company information, including email address, to any outside parties in ways other than disclosed in this privacy statement. 

Next Jump, Inc. uses the information collected on the site to make shopping and promotional activities possible and to enhance your overall experience with Corporate Perks. 

Please contact [Customer Service](https://www.corporateperks.com/feedback/index/uSource/PRIV) for any questions or comments. 

ATTN: Customer Service Department  
Next Jump Inc.   
261 5th Avenue 8th Floor  
New York, NY 10016
